// Target language of the test
export var metaData = {

  // Quiz flag
  flag: "/static/circle-flags/fr.svg",

  // Special characters for this test
  specialCharacters: ['é', 'à', 'è', 'ê', 'ô', 'û', 'â', 'î', 'ü', 'ù', 'ë', 'œ', 'ç', 'ï', 'É', 'À', 'È', 'Ê', 'Ô', 'Û', 'Â', 'Î', 'Ü', 'Ù', 'Ë', 'Œ', 'Ç', 'Ï'],

}



export var cards = {
  "0": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 0 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "0"
  },
  "1": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 1 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "18"
  },
  "2": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 2 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "36"
  },
  "3": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 3 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "54"
  },
  "4": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 4 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "72"
  },
  "5": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 5 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "90"
  },
  "6": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 6 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "108"
  },
  "7": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 7 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "126"
  },
  "8": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 8 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "144"
  },
  "9": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 9 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "162"
  },
  "10": {
    type: 'text',
    question: '18 x 10 = <em>?</em>',
    prompt: "Quel est le résultat ?",
    answer: "180"
  },

};